## **OMOKHOMION EHIS STANLEY**

No 11 Unity street off bayeku road, opposite Banjoko Bus stop Igbogbo, Ikorodu, Lagos Nigeria
Lagos, Nigeria 104211
08130196637
ehizomokhomion@gmail.com

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Client Relationship Management Strategic Marketing Strategic Planning Interpersonal Skills Budget Administration Quality Control Resource Project Management

Passionate educator bringing expertise in educating students on coursework and leading activities to develop career skills. Resourceful in providing diverse instruction focused on real-world applications to prepare students for future. Strategic in offering diverse and engaging coursework that appeals to all students.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Prev Academy Ikorodu, lagos Nigeria

2015 - 2016

Presented engaging lessons and coursework geared toward reaching students with various learning strengths.

Adapted teaching methods and materials to meet students' varying needs and interests.

Collaborated with other teachers to coordinate social activities and field trips in alignment with curriculum.

Planned lessons according to national standards to cover all requirements and prepare for standardised tests.

Created lesson plans and scheduled each day to promote maximum student learning and enrichment.

OMION TECHNICAL COMPANY LTD, Lagos, Nigeria

2011-April 2015

Head of Marketing: Finished Packaging solutions.

Oversaw business development process, which led to increasing customer base by 65% working with the marketing team to target specific products and regions leveraging on market surveys and know-how.

Developed recommendations concerning the strategic plan for growth and cost reduction and presented findings to management based on analysis of cash flow, profit, and customer reviews.

Conducted marketing to increase competitiveness through updates on competitors pricing, industrial developments, and market outreach campaigns. Responsible for client management and satisfaction to ensure the successful closing of deals with existing and new clients.

Developed the framework for the quality control process to ensure that finished product quality meets customer requirements and standards.

Key team leader responsible for management in numerous key areas, including team management supervising and coordinating manufacturing, quality control and customer relations.

## **EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS**

**B.A Music** 

September 2017 – Present

Lagos State University Ojo, Lagos, Nigeria INTERESTS

I am a very active person and try to keep a good work-life balance. My favourite things to do would be cooking, a variety of sports and apart from these I enjoy a good book.